Both teams need to take turns performing.
يجب على الفريقين التناوب في الأداء
Three people act out the song playing at the scene.
ثلاثة أشخاص يؤدون حسب الأغنية المشغلة
They use gestures to interpret it.
ويقومون بتجسيدها بالحركات
One person wears headphones.
شخص واحد يضع سماعات الرأس
Based on teammates' movements,
ويعتمد على حركات زملائه
they must guess the correct song title.
ليخمن اسم الأغنية الصحيح
Let's do a practice round first.
دعونا نجرب جولة أولاً
Rain.
تمطر
In the winter...
في الشتاء
This one...
هذا الذي فعله
This...
هذا
What is this one?
ما هذا الذي فعله؟
That...
ذاك
Say it!
قلها
"Fire in the Winter"
"شعلة في الشتاء"
What's this song called?
ما اسم هذه الأغنية؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
"Men Must Be Strong"
"يجب على الرجل أن يكون قوياً"
Really?
حقاً؟
This is "Men Must Be Strong."
هذه هي "يجب على الرجل أن يكون قوياً"
How do you act out "Men Must Be Strong"?
كيف نمثل "يجب على الرجل أن يكون قوياً"؟
Man.
رجل
Move quickly!
تحرك بسرعة
Get moving!
ابدأ بالحركة
I'll act.
سأمثل
I'll act strong.
سأمثل القوة
Do a set of military boxing.
أؤدي حركات قتالية عسكرية
Martial arts.
فنون قتالية
How do you act this out?
كيف نمثل هذا؟
How do you act out "Men Must Be Strong"?
كيف نمثل "يجب على الرجل أن يكون قوياً"؟
Great joy.
فرح كبير
What's wrong?
ماذا هناك؟
Ear.
أذن
Yellow ear.
أذن صفراء
Huang Jingyu's ear.
أذن هوانغ جينغيو
Yes, that's the song.
نعم، هذه هي الأغنية
If viewers start watching from here,
لو بدأ الجمهور المشاهدة من هنا
they'll think we're filming a foreign show.
سيظنون أننا نصور برنامجاً أجنبياً
What's "yellow ear"?
ما هي الأذن الصفراء؟
Man.
رجل
The first character is right.
الحرف الأول صحيح
Ear.
أذن
The first one is correct.
الأول صحيح
"Man" is correct.
"رجل" صحيح
Second character.
الحرف الثاني
Man ear.
رجل أذن
Ear.
أذن
Man.
رجل
Third character.
الحرف الثالث
Crotch.
فخذ
"Men Must Be Strong"
"يجب على الرجل أن يكون قوياً"
You're a dance major,
أنت طالب رقص
asked to perform a dance,
يطلب منك أداء رقصة
and you just do "crotch." Darn it.
ثم تقوم بحركة الفخذ
Now it's clear.
الآن فهمنا
What's this song?
ما اسم هذه الأغنية؟
"Nine Sisters"
"الأخت التاسعة"
I don't know this.
لا أعرف هذه
We get this.
هذه نفهمها
First character.
الحرف الأول
Drink.
يشرب
No.
لا
Eat.
يأكل
What are you drinking?
ماذا يشرب؟
Medicine.
دواء
What kind of attitude?
ما هي الحالة النفسية؟
Wine.
كحول
"Drunken Butterfly"
"فراشة سكرانة"
Second character.
الحرف الثاني
Wine gone.
لا يوجد كحول
Wine.
كحول
"Nine Sisters"
"الأخت التاسعة"
Call the landlord.
نادِ صاحب الأرض
Grab the landlord.
خذ الأرض
I'll grab.
سآخذها
No.
لا أريد
That "Fight the Landlord"...
تلك لعبة "دوديتشو"
What's this song called?
ما اسم هذه الأغنية؟
Fight the Landlord.
دوديتشو
It's just called "Fight the Landlord."
اسمها دوديتشو
It should be...
يجب أن يكون
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
First two characters.
أول حرفين
Happy.
سعيد
Another kind.
نوع آخر
"Happy Fight the Landlord"
"دوديتشو السعيد"
Heaven gives another five hundred years...
السماء تمنحني خمسمائة سنة أخرى
Heaven gives me another five hundred years.
السماء تعطيني خمسمائة سنة أخرى
Loan.
قرض
Again.
مرة أخرى
What?
ماذا؟
Loan.
قرض
Borrow another five hundred years.
استعارة خمسمائة سنة أخرى
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
Who's the mouse, who's the rice?
من يمثل الفأر ومن يمثل الأرز؟
Bird.
طائر
He definitely won't guess "mouse."
أكيد لن يخمن كلمة "فأر"
I'll be the cat.
سأمثل دور القطة
You just messed up the logic again.
منطقك أربكنا فجأة
You confused everyone with that.
أصبحت الأمور مشوشة بسببه
First two characters.
أول حرفين
Second character.
الحرف الثاني
Cat.
قطة
What is she acting as?
ما الذي تمثله؟
Mouse.
فأر
Second character is "mouse."
الحرف الثاني هو "فأر"
Third character.
الحرف الثالث
What's the third character?
ما هو الحرف الثالث؟
It's "love."
هو "حب"
Love.
حب
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Eating noodles.
يأكل نودلز
Change it.
بدل واحد آخر
Pick another staple food.
غير الطبق الرئيسي
Second character is "mouse."
الحرف الثاني هو "فأر"
Mouse.
فأر
"Mouse Loves Rice"
"الفأر يحب الأرز"
You need some brains for this one.
هذا يحتاج ذكاء فعلاً
"Forget Love Potion"
"ماء النسيان"
Three characters.
ثلاثة أحرف
First character.
الحرف الأول
Confused.
مرتبك
You're guessing the song title.
أنت تخمن اسم الأغنية
Thinking.
يفكر
Looking.
ينظر
Third character.
الحرف الثالث
Third character is "wine."
الحرف الثالث "خمر"
Drink.
يشرب
Forgot to drink wine.
نسي أن يشرب الخمر
"Forget Love Potion"
"ماء النسيان"
Speed up.
أسرع
That.
ذاك
"Drunken Master"
"قبضة السكران"
Guessed it right away.
خمنها فوراً
How did you connect his headphones?
كيف أوصلوا له سماعة المراقبة؟
Two characters.
حرفان
First character.
الحرف الأول
Ball.
كرة
Basket.
سلة
First character is "ball."
الحرف الأول "كرة"
Second.
الثاني
Ball.
كرة
"Prisoner Bird"
"طائر مسجون"
Ball chicken.
دجاجة الكرة
This is too much brainwork.
يتعب العقل جداً
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
First character.
الحرف الأول
Cat.
قطة
King.
ملك
Right.
صحيح
"Queen Ace"
"ورقة الملكة"
Sister.
أخت
She.
هي
"Sister Is Queen"
"الأخت هي الملكة"
He has some knowledge.
لديه بعض المعرفة
Wide and broad.
واسع وفسيح
How many? Seven characters.
كم؟ سبعة أحرف
How do you act out this song?
كيف نمثل هذه الأغنية؟
Pass, poke.
يمر، يطعن
First character.
الحرف الأول
Poke.
يطعن
What's the second character?
ما هو الحرف الثاني؟
Poke sky.
يطعن السماء
Right, third character.
صحيح، الحرف الثالث
Third character.
الحرف الثالث
Big.
كبير
Fourth character.
الحرف الرابع
Road.
طريق
Right.
صحيح
Fifth character.
الحرف الخامس
Sky-piercing road is wide.
طريق السماء واسع
Sixth character.
الحرف السادس
This is left, what's this?
هذا يسار، ما هذا؟
Wide.
واسع
This is left, this is...
هذا يسار، هذا...
Wide noodles.
نودلز عريضة
Left.
يسار
Wide and...
واسع و...
Long.
طويل
Last character.
الحرف الأخير
Wide and heart.
واسع وقلب
Wide and...
واسع و...
Broad.
فسيح
Right.
صحيح
Put it together.
اجمعها معاً
"Sky-Piercing Road Is Wide and Broad"
"طريق السماء واسع وفسيح"
Right.
صحيح
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
This is a story.
هذه قصة
First character.
الحرف الأول
Scatter.
ينتشر
Hold hands.
يمسك اليد
Year.
سنة
Come, Jin Chen acts as "year."
جِن تشن تمثل "سنة"
Act as a catfish.
يمثل سمكة السلور
Year.
سنة
Hold.
يمسك
Involve.
يرتبط
Hold and stick.
يمسك ويلتصق
"Stick" is another pronunciation of the same character.
نفس الحرف لكن بنطق آخر
Hold.
يمسك
Stick.
يلتصق
"Waiting a Thousand Years for Once"
"أنتظر ألف سنة مرة واحدة"
Play that song.
شغل تلك الأغنية
The red-crowned crane song.
أغنية الكركي ذو التاج الأحمر
Let's be red-crowned cranes.
دعونا نكون كركي ذو التاج الأحمر
You act out the crane rescue scene.
مثّلوا مشهد إنقاذ الكركي
You're the little girl.
أنتِ فتاة صغيرة
I'm the little girl.
أنا فتاة صغيرة
I'm the crane.
أنا ذلك الكركي
Okay, you're the crane.
حسناً، أنت الكركي
Then you act as the swamp.
إذاً أنت تمثل المستنقع
Like this.
هكذا أفعل
You act as the swamp.
أنت تمثل المستنقع
Are you really a little girl?
هل أنتِ فعلاً فتاة صغيرة؟
Two characters.
حرفان
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
I'm alive.
لقد عشت
Crane.
كركي سماوي
The toad wants to eat swan meat.
الضفدع يريد أكل لحم البجعة
We're all so vivid and lifelike.
لقد مثلنا بشكل واقعي جداً
Yes.
نعم
He might know about this.
ربما يعرف هذا الأمر
But he can't name it.
لكن لا يستطيع قول الاسم
Right.
صحيح
Time's up.
انتهى الوقت
Gone.
رحل
The one who loves me,
الشخص الذي يحبني
hasn't arrived yet.
لم يأتِ بعد
It must be that flying one.
هذا يجب أن يكون الطائر
"Love Bird"
"حب الطيور"
What's this song called?
ما اسم هذه الأغنية؟
Still a few years older than me.
لا يزال أكبر مني ببضع سنوات
You, move aside.
اذهب بعيداً
Three characters.
ثلاثة أحرف
Heart.
قلب
Love.
حب
The first word is "love," right?
الحرف الأول هو "حب"، صحيح؟
Yes.
صحيح
Can we say the singer too?
هل يمكن ذكر اسم المغني أيضاً؟
Who is this?
من هذا؟
Please.
تفضل
Love.
حب
"Love Bird"
"حب الطيور"
This is...
هذا هو
What is this thing?
ما هذا الشيء؟
Lin Yilun.
لين يي لون
Why is it Lin Yilun?
لماذا هذا لين يي لون؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Lun.
لون
Yilun.
يي لون
"Big Head Son and Small Head Dad"
"الابن ذو الرأس الكبير والأب ذو الرأس الصغير"
Eight characters.
ثمانية أحرف
Big.
كبير
Big head.
رأس كبير
Big-headed kid.
طفل الرأس الكبير
"Big Head Son and Small Head Dad"
"الابن ذو الرأس الكبير والأب ذو الرأس الصغير"
Isn't this that thing?
أليس هذا هو ذلك الشيء؟
"Hello Mr. Billionaire"
"أغنى رجل في مدينة شيهونغ"
Shen Teng.
شن تنغ
Mine doesn't look much like it.
هذا لا يشبهني كثيراً
Calories.
سعرات حرارية
"Burn My Calories"
"أحرق سعراتي الحرارية"
This...
هذا
You can even guess this?
هل استطعت تخمين هذا أيضاً؟
Their young people's language.
لغة الشباب
Meteor.
تدفق
"Meteor Shower"
"مطر الشهب"
How many characters?
كم عدد الأحرف؟
Three characters.
ثلاثة أحرف
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Katyusha is coming, right?
هل جاءت كاتيوشا؟
Hide.
اختبئ
"Meteor Shower"
"مطر الشهب"
Need a smart one too.
يجب أن يكون هناك شخص ذكي أيضاً
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
Heart.
قلب
Love.
حب
I'll act.
سأمثل
I'll act "death," you two act "love."
سأمثل "الموت"، وأنتما تمثلان "الحب"
"Love Even If I Die"
"حتى الموت سأحب"
Yes.
صحيح
"Love Transaction"
"تجارة الحب"
Four characters.
أربعة أحرف
Heart.
قلب
Heart, money.
قلب، مال
Deal the cards.
وزع الأوراق
The second word is "love."
الحرف الثاني هو "حب"
Affection.
مشاعر
"Love Transaction"
"تجارة الحب"
Three characters.
ثلاثة أحرف
Sky Monkey.
قرد يقفز للسماء
"Drop Tower"
"آلة القفز من المبنى"
Let me act out the drop first.
أريد أن أمثل القفز أولاً
How do you act out a drop?
كيف أمثل القفز من المبنى؟
Jump.
اقفز
Bungee.
بنجي
No.
لا
Not that happy.
لست سعيداً جداً
Still "death."
لا يزال "موت"
This kind of "death."
هكذا "موت"
I might not know this song title.
قد لا أعرف اسم هذه الأغنية
You know.
أنت تعرف
I know.
أنا أعرف
Northeast dialect.
لهجة شمال شرق الصين
Groin grab.
أمسك بين الساقين
In Northeast dialect, this is "tao."
في لهجة الشمال الشرقي يسمى هذا "تاو"
This is called...
هذا يسمى
Second word.
الحرف الثاني
Hug.
عانق
Hold.
ضم
Jump.
اقفز
"Drop Tower"
"آلة القفز من المبنى"
Jump "hold" machine.
آلة "القفز والضم"
Switch people.
بدل الشخص
Go act for a bit.
اذهب ومثل
Okay, you take a break.
حسناً، ارتح قليلاً
I should be fine.
يجب أن أكون بخير
Three characters.
ثلاثة أحرف
First word.
الحرف الأول
"Hero Song"
"أغنية الرجل الشجاع"
Great.
رائع
Good, "Hero Song."
جيد، "أغنية الرجل الشجاع"
Is it "Kiss Goodbye"?
هل هي "وداع القبلة"؟
I kiss you, right.
أنا وأنت نقبل، صحيح
"Kiss Goodbye"
"وداع القبلة"
"Journey to the West"
"رحلة إلى الغرب"
"Journey to the West" is called...
اسم "رحلة إلى الغرب" هو
"Dare to Ask Where the Road Is"
"أسأل أين الطريق"
"Journey to the West"
"رحلة إلى الغرب"
Great King.
الملك العظيم
He doesn't know.
هو لا يعرف
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Let's act together.
لنمثل معاً
Act.
مثل
I ask you.
أسألك
Hello.
مرحباً
Where is the road?
أين الطريق؟
Can he hear?
هل يستطيع أن يسمع؟
This way.
هنا
Alright.
حسناً
Sun Wukong.
سون ووكونغ
No, you two need to act "dare."
لا، يجب أن تمثلا "الجرأة"
He doesn't dare ask, you dare ask.
هو لا يجرؤ أن يسأل، أنت تجرؤ
Okay.
حسناً
Dare to ask.
أسأل بجرأة
White Bone Spirit.
شبح العظام البيضاء
What?
ماذا؟
Dare to ask.
أسأل بجرأة
Ground.
أرض
Road.
طريق
"Dare to Ask Where the Road Is"
"أسأل أين الطريق"
Give yourself a like.
أعطِ لنفسك إعجاباً
So scary.
مخيف حقاً
"Dancing Diva"
"راقصة"
Two characters.
حرفان
First word.
الحرف الأول
Five.
خمسة
Second word.
الحرف الثاني
Watch closely.
انظر جيداً
Five circles.
خمس دوائر
Spin.
دُر
If you act like that, don't move up so close.
إذا مثلت هكذا، لا تقترب كثيرًا
Hurry.
أسرع
Wait, isn't there that dance?
أليس هذا فيه تلك الرقصة؟
Yeah, that's the one.
نعم، هذه هي
Spin and leap, I close my eyes.
أدور وأقفز وأنا مغمض العينين
But what's this song called?
لكن ما اسم هذه الأغنية؟
You have First Lady, Second Lady, Third Lady.
لديك السيدة الأولى، الثانية، الثالثة
Fifth Lady.
السيدة الخامسة
Sixth Lady's sister.
أخت السيدة السادسة
Fourth Lady's younger sister.
أخت السيدة الرابعة
Five.
خمسة
"Dance Lady"
"راقصة"
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
I give you two first, you don't want them.
أعطيتك اثنين أولاً، لم تردهما
I give you two, you both don't want them.
أعطيتك اثنين، لم تردهما
Darn it, you only want one.
ثم طلبت واحدًا فقط
Try again.
جرب مرة أخرى
Do it again.
أعدها مرة أخرى
Five characters.
خمسة أحرف
Kiss.
قبلة
The fifth character is "kiss".
الحرف الخامس هو "قبلة"
Right.
صحيح
No extras, just one.
لا أعطي أكثر، فقط واحد
You think they'd play a song twice?
هل تعتقد أن الأغنية ستُشغل مرتين؟
Is that so?
أليس كذلك؟
"Farewell Kiss"
"وداع القبلة"
Darn it, I really don't know this one.
انتهى، فعلاً لا أعرف هذا
Maybe it's really not possible.
ربما فعلاً لا يمكن ذلك
He probably just doesn't know.
ربما هو لا يعرف
It's an age thing for him.
المشكلة في العمر
I don't know anymore.
لا أعرف بعد الآن
Let's switch people.
لنبدل الشخص
Age issue.
مشكلة العمر
Switch to someone else.
بدل شخصًا آخر
Go.
هيا
Look over here.
انظر هنا
Eight characters.
ثمانية أحرف
Isn't there "Big Joy"?
أليس هناك فرحة كبيرة؟
Yeah.
نعم
Forgot.
نسيت
I'm not a girl.
لست فتاة
Come here.
تعال هنا
Look.
انظر
Look over here.
انظر هنا
My look is scary.
مظهري أخافهم
"Dance Lady"
"راقصة"
Lift up your veil.
رفعت غطاء رأسك
Let's act face to face.
لنمثل وجهاً لوجه
Don't look.
لا تنظر
Don't look at this yet.
لا تنظر لهذا أولاً
Look somewhere else.
انظر لمكان آخر
Call me.
نادني
The girl across.
الفتاة المقابلة
Look over here.
انظري هنا
Look at me.
انظري إلي
"Girl Across, Look Over Here"
"الفتاة المقابلة، انظري هنا"
Time's up.
انتهى الوقت
The task is called
اسم المهمة هو
Six people dance each round.
في كل جولة، يرقص ستة أشخاص
Two who draw Dance King
الشخصان اللذان يحصلان على لقب ملك الرقص
know the specific dance scenario.
يعرفان سياق الرقص المحدد
Four who draw The Bluffer
الأربعة الذين يحصلون على لقب المحتال
are basically blank slates.
كأنهم صفحة بيضاء
don't know the actual dance scenario.
لا يعرفون سياق الرقص المحدد
They can only follow the music.
يعتمدون فقط على الموسيقى الحية
Improvise freely.
يؤدون بحرية
After the dance, the scenario is revealed.
يُعلن السياق بعد انتهاء الرقص
The Bluffer can make up stories
يمكن للمحتال أن يختلق الأعذار
to explain their dance moves.
ليشرح حركات رقصه
This way, they hide their identity.
ليخفي هويته
Judges have two chances per round
للحكام فرصتان في كل جولة
to eliminate The Bluffer
ليستبعدوا المحتال
and find the Dance King.
ويكتشفوا ملك الرقص
We'll add an extra round.
سنضيف جولة إضافية
Xiao Bai, stop running.
شياو باي، توقف عن الجري
You're sweating all over.
رأسه مليء بالعرق
Wearing that hat shirtless, not even cold.
يرتدي القبعة بلا قميص ولا يشعر بالبرد
Xiao Bai.
شياو باي
Skip a day of hair styling.
يوم واحد بدون تصفيف شعر
What a hardship.
كم من المعاناة!
Xiao Bai.
شياو باي
Yeah.
صحيح
Rest early after you dance, take a good break.
بعد أن ترقص، ارتح جيدًا
I'm worried you'll get too hot.
أخشى أن تشعر بالحر
That's so abstract.
حقًا مجرد
Here we go again.
عاد هذا مجددًا
It even combines the previous ones.
وارتبط بما سبق أيضًا
This means two backflips, right?
يعني هذا شقلبتان للخلف، صحيح؟
An Yu.
آن يو
Alright, just those two.
حسنًا، هما الاثنان فقط
Hu.
هو
What are you doing?
ماذا ستفعل؟
Are you trying to offend the judges?
هل ستسيء للحكام؟
Is your dance a bit
أليست رقصتك هذه نوعًا ما...
too modern?
حديثة جدًا؟
Just a handshake.
فقط تصافح
Take a few steps.
خطوتان فقط
You'll know once you see the prompt.
ستعرف عندما ترى الموضوع بعد قليل
Don't say anything yet.
توقف عن الكلام الآن
Come on, Big Joy.
هيا، دا شي
Don't bend over.
لا تنحني هكذا
Going for the stream-of-consciousness style.
تلعب بأسلوب تيار الوعي
You're in the same group as me.
أنت من نفس نوعي
Like.
يشبه
Steal.
يسرق
Stealing kids.
يسرق الأطفال
Did I mislead you with this?
هل أكون قد ضللتكم؟
Because there's a heartbeat.
لأن هناك نبض قلب
Really tense.
ضيق جدًا
Super nervous.
متوتر جدًا
That's called modern dance.
هذا يسمى رقص حديث
Not realistic dance.
ليس رقص واقعي
The scenario for this round is
سياق هذه الجولة هو
It's sour, you know.
إنه طعم حامض فعلاً
Xianxu and Jingyu
شيانشو وجينغيو
I think we can eliminate now.
أعتقد أنه يمكننا الإقصاء الآن
Green Lemon Love, bro
حب الليمون الأخضر، يا أخي
Who performed just now?
من الذي مثل قبل قليل؟
Who acted out the sour part?
من جسّد الطعم الحامض؟
Anyu's was so gentle.
كان آنيُ خفيفاً جداً
What was that thing he did?
ما الذي فعله؟ ما هذا الشيء؟
I still have to explain mine.
هل يجب أن أشرح هذا أيضاً؟
Wasn't mine sour? Mine was...
ألم يكن ما فعلته حامضاً؟ ما قدمته؟
No, let me explain first.
لا، دعني أشرح أولاً
Green Lemon Love
حب الليمون الأخضر
From meeting, we walk in.
بدأنا بالتعارف والدخول
Hi, let's add WeChat.
مرحباً، أضفني على ويشات
Just now, you...
أنت قبل قليل...
You didn't have that sly smile before.
لم يكن هناك تلك الابتسامة الماكرة قبل قليل
There was this.
كان هناك هذا
No smile.
لم تكن هناك ابتسامة
Then we hugged.
ثم تعانقنا
Fell into this love.
وانغمسنا في هذه العلاقة
Then, because the green lemon is sour...
ثم لاحقاً بسبب حموضة الليمون الأخضر
Later, wanted to leave.
أردنا الرحيل لاحقاً
But didn't want to go.
لكننا لم نرد الرحيل
Couldn't leave either.
ولم نستطع الرحيل أيضاً
In the end, just smiled helplessly and left.
وفي النهاية، ابتسمنا على مضض ورحلنا
Green Lemon Love is sour.
حب الليمون الأخضر طعمه حامض
It's not a sweet romance.
ليست علاقة حب حلوة
You totally confused me.
لقد جعلتني مرتبكاً تماماً
Mine was pretty straightforward too.
ما قدمته كان واضحاً جداً
Do it again.
أعد التمثيل مرة أخرى
What happened just now?
ماذا حدث قبل قليل؟
When I started, I definitely did this first.
عندما بدأت، فعلت هذا أولاً
First, I acted out the green lemon.
مثلت الليمون الأخضر أولاً
Then I squeezed it a bunch.
ثم بدأت أعصره بقوة
He started with a squeezing move.
هو بدأ بحركة العصر
I kept squeezing non-stop.
أنا عصرت بقوة
I squeezed but couldn't figure it out.
عصرت ولم ألاحظ شيئًا
Just kept squeezing.
عصر قوي
Squeeze.
عصر
Green lemon grew on a cow, is that it?
ليمون أخضر على البقرة، هذا هو؟
No.
لا
Green lemon milk.
حليب الليمون الأخضر
What you did was...
ما فعلته هو
No dance squeezes lemons like that.
أي رقصة لا تعصر الليمون هكذا
Just copying, really.
مجرد تقليد
He totally copied my move.
هو فقط قلد حركتي هذه
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I even did this.
أنا فعلت هكذا أيضًا
Stealing a kid.
سرقة طفل
What a kid.
يا له من طفل جيد
I picked a lemon.
قطفت الليمون
After the lemon, it was so sour.
بعد الليمون يصبح حامضًا جدًا
Yours is just sour.
ما فعلته كان حامضًا
Sour, yeah.
حامض
And then, finally, it's "Love."
وفي النهاية كانت قصة حب
Is there?
هل هناك؟
Yes.
نعم
But hers...
لكن ما فعلته
Hers follows the rules more.
كان أكثر التزامًا بالقواعد
So what was that "goodbye" with me?
إذًا، ما معنى وداعك لنا؟
Xianxu.
شيان شو
Yes.
نعم
Right, explain it to me.
صحيح، فسر لي ذلك
What does shaking hands with us mean?
ما معنى مصافحتك لنا؟
What does "goodbye after handshake" mean?
ما معنى المصافحة ثم الوداع؟
Where's the green lemon?
أين الليمون الأخضر؟
Because I respect the judges.
لأني أحترم الحكام
I had to perform for both judges.
يجب أن أؤدي أمام الحكمين
But what I mean is...
لكن قصدي هو
I think Green Lemon Love is very innocent.
أعتقد أن حب الليمون الأخضر بريء جدًا
There aren't that many moves.
لا يحتاج لكثير من الحركات
No need to act it out.
لا داعي للأداء
Just shake hands and leave.
بعد المصافحة نعود فقط
That's Green Lemon Love.
هذا هو حب الليمون الأخضر
Actually, it's just...
في الحقيقة هو فقط
Hello.
مرحبًا
Me.
أنا
Didn't you see?
ألم ترَ؟
I've been saying goodbye to you.
كنت أودعك طوال الوقت
Because most endings aren't happy.
لأن معظم النهايات ليست جيدة
Goodbye.
وداعًا
After finishing, I even cried here.
بعد الانتهاء بكيت هنا قليلًا
Then I left.
ثم عدت
It's a very sad love story.
إنها قصة حب حزينة جدًا
You didn't even fall in love, why so upset?
أنت لم تعش الحب، لماذا تتألم؟
Just feeling bad here.
أشعر بالحزن هنا
You acted out "please say goodbye."
أداؤك كان "أرجوك وداعًا"
If you put it that way...
إذا قلت ذلك
You performed "judges, goodbye."
كان وداعًا للحكام
That's not Green Lemon Love.
ليس حب الليمون الأخضر
It's just "judges, goodbye."
فقط وداع الحكام
I think it's very innocent.
أشعر أنه بريء جدًا
You're way too innocent.
أنت بريء جدًا
Let me be honest, bro.
سأكون صريحًا يا أخي
Just eliminate me.
فلتقصني إذًا
I'm sure.
أنا متأكد
Yeah.
صحيح
I tried to persuade you, Xiao Hu.
أقنعك يا شياو هو
Definitely eliminating you.
سيتم إقصاؤك بالتأكيد
If only one gets eliminated, it's you.
حتى لو أقصينا شخصًا، سيكون أنت
I wrote "The Bluffer" on my paper.
كتبت "المحتال" على ورقتي
How do you expect me to act?
كيف تريدني أن أؤدي؟
I can only make it up.
سأضطر للاختلاق فقط
Anyu.
آن يو
I just...
أنا فقط
I don't need to.
لا داعي لي
I'm pretty clear, right?
أعتقد أنني واضح الآن
You're not... whatever that was.
أنت لست شيئًا مهمًا
Already forgot your dance, hurry up.
نسيت ما رقصت، أسرع
In my mind...
في مفهومي
It's a very innocent relationship.
هي علاقة بريئة جدًا
So I started with...
لذا بدأت مباشرة بـ
Being naive and shy.
من البراءة والخجل
It's raining.
كان المطر يهطل
Then the two have to part ways.
ثم سيفترق الاثنان
They're leaving school to go home.
سيعودان من المدرسة إلى المنزل
And that's the end.
وهكذا انتهت
Innocence mainly shows naivety.
البراءة تظهر الجهل الطفولي
When you were in high school...
عندما كنت في الثانوية
Saying goodbye to your girlfriend was like this.
الوداع مع صديقتك كان هكذا
Didn't even hold hands.
لا تمسك يدها
Didn't do anything, just like that.
ولا تفعل شيئًا، فقط هكذا
Held hands.
أمسكت يدها
Before parting.
قبل الفراق
I think his isn't as good as mine.
أعتقد أن أدائي أفضل من أدائه
Xiao Bai.
شياو باي
I'm way too direct.
كنت مباشرًا جدًا
Only I acted so directly.
أنا الوحيد الذي كان مباشرًا هكذا
Specifically.
بالتفصيل
Twist gently.
اعصر بلطف
Twist me gently.
اعصرني بلطف
I just...
أنا فقط
Twist gently.
اعصر بلطف
Gentle twist.
عصر لطيف
Green.
أخضر
Green Lemon Love.
حب الليمون الأخضر
I'm starting again.
بدأت من جديد
Didn't you start by jumping?
ألم تبدأ بالقفز أولًا؟
I saw you.
أنا أراقبك
See, it's all in order.
انظر، كل شيء جاء بالترتيب
Green.
أخضر
Two big jumps.
قفزتان كبيرتان
Then...
ثم
Twist gently.
اعصر بلطف
Green Lemon Love.
حب الليمون الأخضر
Modern dance also uses this term, right?
حتى الرقص الحديث يفسر بهذا، صحيح؟
It's also the first character.
أيضًا الحرف الأول
The second character, right?
الحرف الثاني، صحيح؟
Xiao Hu and Chengcheng definitely aren't it.
شياو هو وتشنغ تشنغ ليسا كذلك بالتأكيد
Right.
صحيح
Eliminate those two first.
لنقصيهما أولًا
I'm not.
لست أنا
Yeah.
صحيح
Yours...
ما فعلته أنت
If you go for that harvest joy...
لو اتجهت نحو فرحة الحصاد
You can kind of lean into it.
يمكنك الاقتراب منها
Anyway, you two first.
على أي حال، أنتما أولًا
No problem if I eliminate you two first, right?
لا مشكلة أن أقصيكما أولًا
No problem.
لا مشكلة
Don't say I didn't give you a chance.
لا تقل أني لم أمنحك فرصة
We didn't give you a chance.
نحن من لم نعطك فرصة
Okay.
حسنًا
Daxi, you go first.
دا شي، ابدأ أنت أولًا
I'll go first.
سأبدأ أولًا
Honestly speaking...
بصراحة
That's really impressive.
حقًا مذهل
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
How do I see it...
كيف أرى ذلك؟
Feels like it's at the dance academy.
يبدو وكأننا في أكاديمية الرقص
Like homework from some day.
وكأنها واجب منزلي في يوم ما
I saw barbecue.
رأيت الشواء
Really?
حقًا؟
Anyu.
آن يو
Anyu, come on.
آن يو، تعال
This move is the essence.
هذه الحركة جوهرية جدًا
Bai.
باي
Playing that trick again.
تلعب هذه الخدعة مجددًا
Corn.
ذرة
Dance King again, huh?
ملك الرقص مرة أخرى
Sir Huang.
السيد هوانغ
Sketch.
مسرحية مشهدية
Waiter.
نادل
What kind of magic trick is this?
ما هذا السحر؟
The great live donkey transformation.
تحول الحمار الحي الكبير
Waiter Huang.
النادل هوانغ
Announce the scenario, please.
أعلنوا عن الحالة
Midnight in Qiqihar.
منتصف الليل في تشيتشيهار
It’s eight degrees at night.
في الليل تكون الحرارة ثماني درجات
No one’s acting out the shivers.
لا أحد يمثل الارتجاف
Who knows?
من يعرف؟
Sir Huang, dance it again.
سيد هوانغ، ارقص مرة أخرى
Let me see if it’s related
دعني أرى إذا كان له علاقة
to anything here.
مع ماذا له علاقة؟
Let me check.
دعني أرى
Go to the restaurant at night.
نذهب للمطعم ليلاً
See a buddy, have a drink together.
ترى الأصدقاء وتشرب كأساً
Have a drink over here too.
تشرب كأساً هنا أيضاً
We’re all friends.
كلهم أصدقاء
There are skewers on the table.
ثم هناك أسياخ على الطاولة
I’ve got friends over there.
لدي أصدقاء هناك أيضاً
Grab some skewers and head over.
أخذ بعض الأسياخ وأذهب إليهم
You two, go ahead and eat.
أنتما كُلاكما، كُلا
You two just keep drinking.
أنتما فقط تشربان
Alright, you two drink.
حسناً، أنتما اشربا
Have you ever gone to a restaurant?
ذهبت للمطعم، هل جربت ذلك؟
Someone brings you food from another table.
يأخذون طعامهم من طاولة أخرى ويعطونك
They bring it over.
يأتون به إليك
Will you eat it? Here you go.
هل تأكل؟ خذ، لك
Dandong.
داندونغ
Dandong has this custom.
في داندونغ هناك هذا التقليد
Dandong does.
داندونغ لديها ذلك
Drinks and food go hand in hand.
الطعام والمشروب لا ينفصلان
Everyone here is a friend.
الجميع هنا أصدقاء
All friends.
كلهم أصدقاء
Daxi, tell us about yours.
داشي، أخبرنا عن حالتك
It’s night, the lights are bright.
في الليل، الإضاءة ساطعة جداً
Brighter than daytime.
أكثر سطوعاً من النهار
The restaurant’s lights are really bright.
إضاءة هذا المطعم ساطعة جداً
And then
ثم
And then it’s
ثم يكون
What’s this?
ما هذا؟
Sprinkling salt?
يرشون الملح
I thought it was grilled chicken neck.
ظننت أنهم يشوون رقبة الدجاج
Daxi’s vibe kind of fits.
داشي، هذا الإحساس قريب قليلاً
But she
لكنها
Was Daxi the first to dance?
هل داشي رقص أولاً؟
Yes.
نعم
I just want to confirm if she is.
أردت فقط التأكد إذا كانت هي
Anyu.
آنيُو
I think Daxi’s
أعتقد أن حالة داشي
should be the same as mine.
يجب أن تكون مثل حالتي
Anyway, me too.
على أي حال، أنا أيضاً
I’ll go first.
سأبدأ أولاً
I just thought of Qiqihar elements.
فكرت بكل عناصر تشيتشيهار
Went through all of them.
تذكرتهم جميعاً
There are skewers.
هناك أسياخ
Qiqihar skewers are just a chunk of meat, right?
أسياخ تشيتشيهار قطعة لحم واحدة، صحيح؟
No.
لا
Yours is about the same as Daxi’s today.
حالتك اليوم مثل حالة داشي تقريباً
You can’t do it like that.
لا يمكنك فعل ذلك هكذا
It’s definitely one skewer, then you start.
أكيد تبدأ بسيخ واحد ثم تتابع
And the weather is clear and fresh.
ثم يكون الجو صافياً ومنعشاً
A skewer of meat.
سيخ لحم واحد
After skewering, he tosses it up.
بعد أن ينتهي، يرفع السيخ للأعلى
When he danced just now,
عندما كان يرقص حينها
I don’t think his was like that.
أعتقد أن طريقته ليست مشابهة
I don’t think Anyu is.
أعتقد أن آنيُو ليس كذلك
Xiaobai, tell us about yours.
شياو باي، أخبرنا عن حالتك
Mine is even more specific.
كنت أكثر تحديداً
He’s more specific again, go ahead.
هو أيضاً كان محدداً، هيا
I am
أنا
Home now, feeling happy.
عدت للبيت، سعيد
He’s like you.
هكذا يكون أنت
Can Teng run home like that?
هل يستطيع تنغ العودة للبيت جرياً؟
And then
ثم
Barbecue, eating barbecue.
شواء، أكل الشواء
Have a little drink.
شرب كأس صغير
Drink a bit too much.
شرب أكثر من كأس
Remembered today’s Dance King event.
تذكرت أمر ملك الرقص اليوم
I think Xiaobai’s could be it.
أعتقد أن حالة شياو باي ربما تكون
Who dares?
من يجرؤ؟
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
You get it, right?
هل فهمت؟
I think it’s like Xiaobai and Jin Chen.
أعتقد أنها مثل شياو باي وجين تشن
Okay.
حسناً
Xiaobai and Jin Chen are
شياو باي وجين تشن هما
the ones with words.
هناك كلمات
Congratulations, you got it right.
مبروك، الإجابة صحيحة
Got on the kang bed.
صعد إلى السرير